Doug MacGregor Papers
Doug MacGregor Papers
- Syracuse University cartoons and illustrations
  - Cartoons, 1976-1979; undated (Oversize 3)
    SU5 SU vs. Wisconsin Badgers in football 1976 - original/pen and ink/pencil
    SU6 SU vs. St. Bonaventure in basketball 1976 - original/pen and ink/pencil
    SU7 SU vs. Rutgers Scarlet Knights 1976 - original/pen and ink/pencil
    SU8 SU vs. North Carolina St. Wolfpack in football 1976 - original/pen and ink/pencil
    SU9 SU vs. Rutgers Scarlet Knights in basketball 1978 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    SU10 SU vs. LeMoyne Dolphins in basketball 1979 - original/gouache and ink
    SU11 SU vs. W. Virginia Mountaineers in basketball 1978 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    SU12 SU vs. W. Virginia Mountaineers in football 1978 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    SU13 SU vs. Illinois in football 1978 Daily Orange newspaper clipping
    SU14 SU vs. St. Bonaventure in basketball 1978 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen (includes issue of the Daily Orange in which the cartoon was published)
    SU15 SU vs. Maryland Terrapins in football 1977 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen (includes issue of the Daily Orange in which the cartoon was published)
    SU16 SU vs. Maryland Terrapins in football 1977 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    SU17 SU vs. Maryland Terrapins in football 1978 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    SU18 SU vs. Pittsburgh Panthers in football 1977 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    SU19 SU vs. Boston College Eagles in football 1977 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    SU20 SU vs. Pittsburgh Panthers in football 1978 - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    [unnumbered] SU vs. Washington Huskies - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    [unnumbered] SU vs. Penn State (Nittany Lions) - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
    [unnumbered] SU vs. University of Virginia Cavaliers - original/pen and ink/Zipatone screen
- Publications
  - The Best of Sunny Side Up, 2001; collection of MacGregor's cartoons (Box 1)
    Transfer from University Archives, 2018.
  - A Collection of MacGregor Editorial Cartoons from the Norwich Bulletin, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Daily Orange issue, 19 Dec 1952 (Oversize 4)
  - Daily Orange issues with cartoons by Doug MacGregor, 30 Sep 1977; 21 Oct 1977,; 28 Oct 1977,; 10 Nov 1977,; circa 1976-1979; includes one undated special basketball supplement; 5 items (Oversize 4)
  - Hurrican Season Cartoons, 2004; collection of MacGregor's cartoons (Box 1)
  - Orange Crush magazine, Apr 1977; first edition of the magazine (Oversize 4)
  - Morgan McKinney was Portly, not Skinny: A Christmas Story, 2003; written and illustrated by MacGregor (Box 1)
  - The Refrigerator Door Gallery, 1996; collection of MacGregor's cartoons (Box 1)
  - Report issues, Mar 1978; 10 Apr 1978,; 10 Oct 1978,; 6 Nov 1978; MacGregor was art director for this publication (Oversize 4)
  - SU Hoops, Jan-Feb, 1979; two issues with cover and cartoons by MacGregor; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Syracuse Poems, 1976 (Oversize 4)
  - Syracuse Poems and Stories, 1977 (Oversize 4)
  - Syracuse Review, 1978 (Oversize 4)
- Clippings
  - Daily Orange sports cartoons by Doug MacGregor, 23 Sep 1977; 14 Oct 1977,; 11 Nov 1977,; 29 Sep 1978,; circa 1976-1979; 6 items (Oversize 4)
  - Norwich Bulletin matted clippings about MacGregor, undated; 2 items (Oversize 4)
  - Syracuse Herald Journal article about changes to Syracuse University Saltine Warrior mascot, 1 Sep 1978 (Oversize 4)
  - Miscellaneous, clippings from Daily Orange, other papers; accompanied by letter from MacGregor to Syracuse University Archives (Box 1)